flashcardexchange.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy

At Flashcard Exchange, we take your privacy concerns regarding our service seriously, so we have created the following Privacy Policy to explain our information collection and use practices. Our Privacy Policy covers what information we collect through our service, how we use this information, how you may opt-out of this collection, the security measures we take to protect this information, and our policy regarding children under 13 years of age. By using our service, you consent and agree to the information collection and use practices described in our Privacy Policy. We may periodically make changes to our Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to review the most recent version of our Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it.

## What Information Is Collected?

We may collect information from you through our website, and when you purchase or register for our service. Below are the specific details on what, where, when, and why this information is collected and how it is used.

## Registration

The term “personally identifiable information” means any information that may be used to identify you, including, but not limited to, your name, address, email address, Internet Protocol address, phone number, billing information, or other contact information. You may be asked for certain personally identifiable information when registering for or accessing a particular product or service. We do not share this information with any third parties.

## Flashcard Exchange Database

Flashcard Exchange is used to create flashcards. We store this data in our database. We use this information in aggregate to generate statistics and other usage information. We share this information with you, other end users, and other third parties.

## Advertisements

Flashcard Exchange displays advertising served from the Google Adsense program. They request the following information be added to the Flashcard Exchange privacy policy:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.flashcardexchange.com. 
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Flashcard Exchange users based on their visit to www.flashcardexchange.com and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

Update your [Google Ad Preferences](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences) to control the ads you see.

## Cookies

Cookies are small text files stored by your browser on your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to improve our website and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize you and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change your browser settings to refuse them. You may change your browser’s settings to refuse our cookies. However, if you do so, you may not be able access certain Flashcard Exchange services.

## Use of Contractors

We may retain the service of outside contractors to perform services on our behalf (for example, to help provide technical support services or deliver new products or services). At times, we must disclose relevant personally identifiable information about you to our contractors so they may provide these specific services for us. We require our contractors to keep this information confidential and to only use the information on our behalf.

## Email Communications

Periodically, we may send email to you if you have indicated a preference to receive news, updates, special offers, and other information relating to our service. You may unsubscribe from these email subscriptions at the profile web page for your account on our website.

## Updating Your Information

If you desire to change or modify any of the information that you have previously provided to us, you may do so at the Account Info web page for your account on our website.

## Children

Our service are intended solely for persons 13 years of age and older. If you are under the age of 13 you may not access or use our service. By using our service you represent and warrant to us that you are 13 years of age or older.

## Links to Third Party Web Sites

Our service may contain links to other websites and software. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites or software. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order o understand their privacy and information collection practices.

## Disclosures Required by Law

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe in good faith that an applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it, or when we believe disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of another user.

## Mergers and Acquisitions

In the event that we or a portion of our assets are acquired by another company, customer information, including personally identifiable information, may be one of the transferred assets.

## No Error-Free Performance

We do not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve our service generally. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it. We will not be liable for any damages, including incidental, consequential, or punitive damages, relating to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

Copyright © 2001-2012 Collective Research
